In the not-too-distant future
Next Sunday, AD
There was a guy named Joel
Not too different
than you or me
He worked at
Gizmonic Institute
Just another face in
a red jumpsuit
He did a good job
cleaning up the place
But his bosses didn't like him
So they shot him into space
We'll send him cheesy movies
The worst we can find
La-la-la
He'll have to sit and
watch them all
And we'll monitor his mind
La-la-la
Now keep in mind Joel
can't control
Where the movies begin or end
La-la-la
Because he used those
special parts
To make his robot friends
Robot Roll Call
Cambot
Pan left
Gypsy
Hi, girl
Tom Servo
What a cool guy
Croooow
He's a wisecracker
If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
and other science facts
La-la-la
Then repeat to yourself
It's just a show
I should really just relax
For Mystery Science
Theater 3000
(guitar strumming)
(steam hissing)
(creaking)
(fire crackling)
(door sliding)
(door grinding)
(loud clicking)
(bolt grinding)
(door slamming)
- Hi everybody, I'm
Joel Robinson
and these are my
robots and friends,
Gypsy, Crow.
- Hi.
- And Tom Servo and
it's casual day up here
on the satellite o' love,
so for this segment,
we're gonna wing it.
- Hmm.
- Sure.
- Sounds like fun, that's great,
good.
- Yep.
- So, (laughing) wing it.
Ah.
- Hmm?
- What?
- Nothing.
- I thought you were, oh.
- Mmm mmm.
- Hey.
- What, what, what?
- Oh, I forgot.
- Oh.
- Well, uh.
- [Ship] Commercial
signing in five seconds.
Commercial sign now.
We'll be right back.
- What she said.
- Pretty.
- [Announcer] Call now.
(humming)
- Hey, look at that.
- Oh, the Thompson
twins are calling.
- Eh, yes, gotta go.
Yes, Joel.
Insert perfunctory
acknowledgment here.
Joel, my invention today is
for all the right reasons,
because stress levels aren't
high enough in America,
because people need to know
how very important you are
and because you may be in
line for a movie
when that important project
deadline comes and goes.
I'm talking about the
cellular desk.
You see, with the cellular
desk I can live my job.
Why I can take an
intimidating meeting anywhere.
Why just today I was
out for walk,
going through some files
and I realized
that it had been awhile since
Frank's last employee review.
Frank, (buzzing) could
I see you in my office?
- [Frank] I'm right here.
- Ah, Frank, take a seat.
Frank, I was just going
through some files
and I realized it had been
awhile since your last review,
(buzzing) Frank, could
I see the Frank file?
- I'm right here.
- Ah, uncooperative.
(papers plopping)
Hostile.
(chair creaking)
Uncoordinated.
Ah, Frank, Frank, Frank.
(groaning)
Well, bear witches?
- Hmm, I'm glad we're hourly.
- Yeah, you know John
Lennon said sirs,
instant karma's
going to get you,
but now you can get
Instant Karma.
- Ha, ha, that's right, Joel.
What goes around comes around,
but now you don't have
to wait for it.
And no more confusion
about what incident
correlates to what action,
just watch.
- Oh, say Joel?
- Hmm-mm?
- I just sent my whole
allowance to Sally Struthers.
- Oh, to sponsor a child?
- No, for her.
I just feel sorry for her.
- Sure, we all do.
Well, let's check out what
your karma is, mister.
- Simply pour contents into
a medium sized mixing bowl,
add water and presto,
there's your Instant Karma.
- Oh wow, strawberry licorice?
- Great, wow!
Uh, how 'bout this?
Servo, I cleaned up
your room today,
'cause I know your arms
are useless and everything.
- Oh, what, the, the, thanks,
I think.
- Oh, no problem.
- Alright, let's see
what happens.
Add a little water
- Smells good!
- to the Instant Karma.
- Ahh.
- Okay, anything happenin'?
- Joel, I can't
really explain it,
but I've got this incredible
sense of inner peace
and wellbeing.
- And a Snickers bar.
Here you go, Crow.
- Whoa.
- You lucky duck, wow man.
- You know, Tom Servo,
there's also bad karma.
- Oh, yeah?
- Uh yeah, remember
the other day
when you borrowed
Crow's Danskin?
You stretched it and then
pitted it out.
Well, uh.
- So?
- Let's see what happens.
We'll add a little
water in here.
- What could possibly
happen to me for that one?
- Mix it up.
Yep, here it comes.
- Oh, no, my aunt's comin'
to take me
to the Michael Bolton concert.
- Yes, yes.
(laughter)
- Oh, man, I'm really sorry.
- Well, we've got some
pretty good karma
goin' on up here on the
Satellite o' Love.
What do ya think, sirs?
Hmm?
- Think you've got good karma,
ay?
Then how come you're
going to be watching
another Hercules film?
And the very first
Hercules film.
The one that started it all.
(menacing laughter)
Well, we all shine on,
don't we Mr. Robinson?
Frank, send in the movie.
- I'm right, doh.
- Frank.
Oh, absent.
(chanting and bell jingling)
(electronic beeping)
(yelling)
- Ah, we got movie time.
- Movie time, movie time!
(loud clicking)
(door rolling)
(bolt grinding)
(door grinding)
(door slamming)
(hinge creaking)
(rhythmic buzzing)
- [Joel] Hey, looks
like a high school play.
- [Crow] Yeah, it does.
- [Tom] Remember, today's
Hercules, made from genuine
Steve Reeves parts.
Sylvia Koscina says
Sylvia's mmm.
My movie has a first name
It's O-S-C-A-R, I, oh
- [Tom] Real musical, huh?
- [Crow] Stevens Hawkings
presents The Silly String
Theory.
- [Crow] Hey look, there's
the constellation Feces
right below Taurus the bull.
Oh, now that's not the dog,
I don't think.
(thunder claps)
- [Joel] Oh, Ted Turner's
colorizing the universe now.
- [Group] Hercules.
- [Crow] Ah, it's bigger.
Last night
I think we've seen
this all before
- [Crow] Oh he's the
finder of lost loves.
- [Joel] That's
James Franciscus.
- [Tom] And so where's
the bouncing ball?
Are we supposed to be
singing now?
Gods to whom he
- [Crow] Yet even he suffered
from painful hemorrhoids.
- [Joel] You know I got the
feeling Hercules is gonna
learn a important lesson
and kick some serious butt.
- [Tom] My mortal
weakness is cheesecake.
(laughter)
Let's watch on.
- [Crow] Oh, I hope they
aren't Herc's mortal weakness.
(flute music)
- [Joel] Pan flute master
Zamfir was arrested today,
naked and drunk, running
through a goat herd.
(bleating)
(horse whinnying)
- [Tom] Flicker.
No.
(wheels scraping)
(horses whinnying)
- [Crow] Kibbles 'n bits,
kibbles 'n bits,
gotta get me some
kibbles 'n bits.
(screaming)
- [Joel] Put it in second.
- [Crow] Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- [Tom] That's a guy.
It's a student driver.
Yech.
- [Tom] (dramatic humming)
- [Joel] Hey, she
dropped an egg.
- [Tom] Hmm, it's so deli--
- [All] Oh, oh, oh.
- [Tom] Say.
- [Crow] Hey Herc, got a match?
- [Joel] Not since
Superman died.
(horse hooves galloping)
- [Tom] Well that's either
Herc or Joe Piscopo.
Can't tell.
(dramatic music)
(horse blowing)
- [Joel] Great shot.
- [Crow] Wait, this is
ancient Greece.
They didn't have ruins yet.
- [Tom] Oh wow, hmm.
Eddie Rabbitt.
Hmm.
I'm drivin' my life away
Huh?
- [Crow] Oh, it's a Dodge.
- [Joel] Ram tough.
- [Crow] I'll just chuck 'er.
- [Tom] Hey, who's
gonna pay the fare here?
- [Joel] Why it's a
Comfo-Rest Adjustable Rock.
- [Crow] Does this bug you?
Flink.
- [Tom] Oh, oh, oh, oh.
I went home with you?
- I thank you.
And I thank the gods for
having brought you here today
and for saving me.
- I must admit, I was
frightened for you,
watching those runaway horses.
- [Joel] Have I mentioned
I'm immense and immortal?
- How do you feel?
- Better.
- [Crow] Did I get
anything on my butt?
- I'm still trembling, I guess.
What's the matter?
Why do you sit and stare
at me like that?
- [Tom] Well, huh, huh,
you know it.
- I don't know, so few
women come this way.
- [Joel] With so few clothes.
- And so?
- As long as you're here,
I might as well.
I never saw a girl
more beautiful.
- Oh.
- [Tom] Sweet talker.
- [Hercules] I've
come a long way.
Seeing you is worth it.
- How simple men are.
- [Crow] Tell him sister.
- As though I were a
plant or an animal.
- [Tom] Can I water you?
- Still, I thank you, you know.
- [Joel] Oh, looks like
an early Bay Watch.
- I'm telling you the truth,
don't thank me for it.
- [Crow] Thank my
personal trainer.
- [Tom] So, uh, wanna look
for agates or something?
- You couldn't be anyone
but Hercules the Theban.
- [Crow] Thank you.
- I know you're expected.
Everything will change,
they say.
- I, (sniffing)
- [Tom] Holy cow I'm hungry,
I gotta go.
- [Hercules] By the gods,
everything's burnt by this time.
- [Crow] Still, Lassie
will taste good right now.
- [Joel] Ew.
- [Crow] Sit, stay.
- No, well done, perhaps.
- [Tom] Here, want some meat?
No Pace picante sauce?
Get the rope.
- Will you have a piece?
- [Crow] Of that?
- Go on.
- [Tom] Come on, taste it all.
- [Crow] Yech, this is
really weird, Herc.
- Go on.
- No more, thank you.
- [Joel] I'm on Jenny Craig.
- I will start where
your lips have touched.
- Why how dare you be
so audacious?
- I'm too hungry to help it.
- [Crow] It's my piece o' meat,
I'll bite it where I want to.
(sloppy lipsmacking)
- [Tom] Hey, long as
you're over there,
hook me a Primo outta the
fridge, will ya?
- [Joel] Pig.
- [Tom] Thor, hey buddy.
- [Crow] Oh, wouldn't you know,
a flat.
- [Tom] Hey, you
gotta box wrench?
- That is no work
for a princess.
Yes, you are Iole, daughter
of Pelias, king of Julco.
The royal standard on the
chariot told me your name.
- [Joel] I used to lift
with your brother.
- Here, let me do it.
I can work much faster.
- There's lots of time.
To return to a city
that I hate so.
- [Crow] Detroit?
- That's no way to
welcome a stranger.
- Only you've no
right to be here.
- Your father knows about it.
- He didn't ask you.
It was a question of teaching
the art of war to a fetus,
my brother, and you offered to.
- [Joel] A fetus?
- Isn't that the same thing?
- No, you know the
story of my family.
A man named Brady
- Somebody spoke to
you about us.
- [Joel] Did Jean tell
you I liked you?
- You remember it well, then.
Ah yes, I remember it well
- Was it really so bad?
- [Crow] Excuse me while I
have a strange interlude.
- I remember it now.
- [Tom] Uh oh.
I remember all that went on.
- [Joel] (heavy sign) Oh boy.
- Is it wrong to be as
happy as I was then?
But the gods won't answer
that question.
- [Crow] It's a simple yes
or no woulda been fine.
- They turn from me when I ask.
I was only a child that day,
10 years ago.
- [Crow] Previously,
on Hercules.
- [Iole] It had been such
a happy afternoon for me.
We were returning from the
hunt with my Uncle Aeson,
who was king of Julco
at that time.
He insisted that his son
Jason ride in his chariot,
together with my brother
Iphitos, my father and I.
- [Tom] And the horses,
don't forget us.
- [Iole] At our side rode the
captain of the escort, Chiron,
who had had angry words with
the king on the previous day.
- [Crow] I'm angry.
- [Iole] And we did not
know what it was about.
(horse hooves clopping)
In the woods,
- Guard, halt.
Left face.
- [Iole] We suddenly
saw a platoon
of soldiers coming toward us.
- [Tom] Hey, I found a pack
of Trojans in the road.
- [Iole] There was a
man in chains.
- [Joel] (laughing)
That's disgusting.
- [Crow] Look what you did, bad.
- [Iole] My uncle
stopped the chariot.
I tried to see the face
of the prisoner,
but he knelt with his
head bent very low.
The king whispered something
in my father's ear.
As my father got down
from the chariot
and went to talk with the
officer of the platoon.
- [Joel] Ah, but first he
pulled his skirt
out of his underpants.
- What is he charged with?
- [Tom] Blocking the road.
- [Guard] He killed a
woman and robbed her
of what little money she
had, your Excellency.
- [Joel] Oh oui, I
did that thing.
- [Tom] Hmm, wrap him up,
I'll take him.
- You like to kill, ay?
- [Iole] To kill, that
was the only word
I was able to understand
of the brief conversation
that followed.
But I knew somehow that the
man must be condemned to death.
- [Crow] It's a murderer,
nothin' to worry about.
- [Iole] My father came
back to the chariot,
and whispered
something to my uncle.
- [Tom] Excuse me, are
you Hector Elizondo?
- [Iole] The king shook his
head and we started off again.
(goofy twang singing)
- The thought of person as dead
swept over me like a bad omen.
- [Crow] Three, the
final conflict.
- [Tom] Dark and stormy night.
- [Iole] Later on, my sleep
was filled with nightmares.
The memory of what happened in
the woods would not leave me.
Again and again, I pictured
what would certainly
be the end of that
terrible storm.
- [Crow] Yeah, never
eat Mexican at bedtime.
- [Iole] The
condemned man brought
to the place of execution.
The executioner
advancing to him.
Grasping his ax.
- [Tom] Breakfast.
- [Iole] Lifting the ax
and me powerless to help.
(screaming)
- [Joel] I dreamed I
kissed Gavin McLeod.
- [Iole] I heard the scream.
I heard other screams echoing
from the farthest end
of the pass.
(muffled wailing)
My terror was even greater
when I noticed that my
nurses' bed was empty.
- [Tom] Yeah, there was
a real servant problem
in ancient Greece.
- [Crow] I decided to put
on some socks.
My feet were freezing.
- [Iole] I was out of my
mind with fear.
I ran to the throne room.
- [Tom] It's a going out
of business sale.
We've lost our empire and
everything is priced to move.
- [Iole] I could scarcely
see the body of the king
as they carried him out amidst
the clamor and confusion.
- [Tom] Oh boy.
- [Iole] My father stood there,
petrified.
- [Joel] Oh, who bled here?
Get me some club soda.
- [Iole] Then he turned and a
look of fear crossed his face.
For the stand behind the
throne was empty.
- [Tom] Looks like a Jim
Dine sculpture.
- [Iole] The Golden
Fleece was gone.
- [Joel] But I digress,
how was your day?
- Jason escaped with the
Golden Fleece.
(snoring)
And Chiron, too, but you
know the rest.
- So that's why Chiron was
accused of killing the king,
kidnapping Jason and
stealing the Golden Fleece.
- Yes.
- And for what reason?
- [Iole] For revenge.
- And you believe that?
- It's important.
Do you think that people lie?
- [Tom] No, never.
Yes, always.
- Well, I've heard it wasn't
Chiron who killed the king.
It was the king's
brother who murdered him.
- That's not true.
- Why do you relive the
story if it's not true?
- [Crow] Hey, my turd
bag's full over here.
Can ya empty this thing?
- They all speak about
the past here.
The murder happened to
put my father
on his brother's throne.
But I know he wouldn't do that.
Tragic.
Now that the Golden Fleece
is gone, he must officiate.
- [All] Ew.
- But when you try to aid
them, why they don't care.
My poor father's above
your suspicions.
- For all our sakes, I hope so.
- [Joel] Anyway, this should
hold 'til you get to Sparta.
- I see you're joking.
- [All] Ah, ha, ha, ha.
- I remember somebody saying
you're a friend of Chiron.
Have you come for revenge?
And more suffering?
- Wait, would you allow
me to accompany you?
- [Tom] On piano?
- Please.
- [Crow] Let's start the movie.
- I'm not much of a carpenter.
It won't work.
It's better to let me
take you back to Julco.
- [Tom] There's a new
Sophocles play opening tonight.
- Come with me, please?
- [Crow] Pretty please,
with Herc on top?
- I would like to see your eyes
with happiness there in
place of hate.
Because I can understand
just the way you feel,
but I will help you now.
Believe me.
I'll protect you.
- [Joel] Um, Hercules,
tell me again.
Why didn't we take the chariot?
- [Crow] Can we stop
at a SuperAmerica soon?
- [Tom] It's okay, just hush.
Hercules now concludes
his broadcasting day.
Good night, and may Herc bless.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Where is the sample?
- [Joel] Oops, boy I'd hate to
shovel those steps, ya know?
Just whoa.
- [Tom] Hi, Hercules,
reservation for two.
It might be under
Heracles though.
- [Joel] Oh, no, really,
they take this cheese,
they get it really hot,
and then they pour retsina
all over the top, and then they
light it and they say, opa.
- As the worm eats the
fruit that matures.
- [All] Ew.
- As men stalk their prey,
he will come here for you.
When you see the man,
he will wear one sandal.
Wait no longer.
- [Crow] She has a
creamy strawberry center.
- Will you escape destruction?
He wears but a single sandal.
When he comes, take care.
- But why does he hate
me like that?
- He does not know you
are the man he hates.
- Oh, father,
how can you take stock in
these oracles?
And this one isn't even pretty.
- Destiny knows about all men,
and when you're time comes,
you too will know.
- You witch, get away,
do you hear?
- They will speak no more.
When someone angers the gods,
they finish.
- Why--
- No.
- [Tom] Can we not fight
just this once?
- Iphitus, respect the
gods and their oracles.
They are the gods messengers.
- [Crow] Just askin'
about the oracle.
- I shall give an order
that any man coming to Julco
(chattering)
You.
- [Crow] How long have
you been there?
- Who is that?
- Hercules, the master of
arms that you sent for.
- Hercules the Theban.
- [Joel] Hey, I'm no Thebe.
- [Pelias] Come forward.
- [Crow] May I take
your luggage?
- [Joel] You're next.
(mysterious warbling tone)
- Welcome to Julco.
- [Tom] A planned community.
- They say you're almost a god.
Well then, why aren't
you invisible?
- Stop it Iphitus.
This man saved my life today.
- Marvelous, that's a way
to make a fine impression.
- You better listen to what
I have to say to Hercules,
because it concerns you, too.
You're here to reinforce Julco.
- [Crow] Done.
And?
- Hercules will guide you
until you're able to reign.
But I, he must show you.
Because I want to give
the throne up.
- Father.
- [Crow] Princess, please.
- Because each year I
grow more anxious.
I can't go on being
king forever.
I can't go on.
- [Tom] I'll go on.
- Father, you've been
drinking too much tonight.
- I guess you're right,
but it won't stop it,
can't you see?
(burping)
Hercules, I must beg
you to help us at Julco.
- [Crow] Just said you were
drinkin' too much, geez.
- You must help to keep
the throne for my boy here.
If I find that you are loyal,
I will grant you anything
you want out of Julco.
- [Tom] Anything?
- I hope you will sleep well.
(snuffling)
One moment, he may be an
imposter, how do I know?
- [Joel] Have another drink,
dad.
- But I saw him.
My horses, they were
running away.
- [Crow] Here, benchpress me.
- He stopped my horses.
I knew who he was.
- Certainly.
- [Joel] Why, he could
be Roy Rogers.
- And I'm truly grateful.
But I can't depend on the
eyes of a girl.
- What are you trying to say?
- [Tom] I'm a pig.
- Nothing.
Don't be upset about it, Iole.
- [Crow] Why don't we talk
about it later.
- Well then, let me
do it father.
- [Joel] You a billiards man,
Herc?
- Alright then, prove
yourself fearless.
Come on.
- [Crow] What are you doin'?
That's my good spear.
(grunting and groaning)
- [Tom] I'll bend it back later.
(metal clanging)
- Good, Hercules.
- [Crow] Sit, Hercules.
- Enough now.
Iole may show you to
your quarters.
- Until tomorrow, Pelias.
- [Joel] Well here's where
the workin' out pays off.
- Why do you have to treat
me as if I were a baby?
(sniveling and mewling)
He's taken you in, just
as he's charmed Iole.
- And you have him because
you're weak and impulsive.
- [Tom] I'm not.
Am I?
- Hercules is a guarantee.
He's more than a match
to play against Argos,
Laertes, Tifi, Dijustria,
and all those others
who plan to get the
throne of Julco.
I want that throne for you.
- [Crow] Ooh, I want
that throne.
(steam hissing)
(door slamming)
(crackling)
(swishing)
(rolling)
(door closing)
(clamping)
(slamming)
(hissing)
- Joel, what was the deal
with the ancient Greeks, huh?
- Hey be careful, you're talkin'
about
the ancient Greeks, Crow.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But this constellation jazz,
come on.
After 2000 years, can
we finally admit
the emperor has no clothes?
Four stars, oh, it's
a great pair.
Right, or Cassiopeia,
whatever the heck that is.
- Hey, what about Orion?
- Okay, okay, I'll
give ya Orion.
I gotta admit, Orion's alright,
but the rest of 'em, it
just doesn't--
- (throat clearing) If I
could step in here, please.
Lest we despoil the reputation,
Crow,
of the founders of
democracy too much.
The reason you don't see the
same figures in the night sky
is because new constellations
have never been identified
to reflect modern tastes
and sensibilities.
- You've done that?
- I've done that.
A little help here, Joel?
Uh, watch carefully.
The first grouping of stars
found in the southern sky,
forms a constellation for even
the simplest hayseed, Crow.
Yes, it's a ham sammich.
Fascinatingly, the star to
the left of the main group
forms a perfect pickle.
Next.
As winter gives way to spring,
the eastern sky is
ablaze with the glory of
the New Christy Minstrels.
- New Christy Minstrels?
Who woulda ever thought that?
- Well, that's why you
need people like me
and the Greeks, Joel, next.
- Oh brother.
- Sophist.
Dodi Siemen just may be
tempted to once again
navigate by the stars,
when they recognize in
this group of 11,
Guernica, Picasso's
cubist masterpiece,
portraying the horrors
of the Spanish Civil War.
- Well, talk about your
modern sensibilities.
Really good job, Tom Servo,
for these renovations
of old constellations.
- And I've salvaged the
reputations of the ancient
Greeks.
- Well done.
- Tom, I regret my
earlier sniping
and if you'll allow me, I got
a constellation here, Joel?
- Oh, well that's really n--
- Here, it's a pencil.
- Doh.
- The eraser's almost gone.
- Crow, don't mock me.
You're playin' with fire.
- Hey, two dots, it's a pencil.
What could be more modern?
- I weep for the death of
the spirit and the soul.
- Hey, who doesn't?
We'll be right back.
- En oui
- [Joel] Ah, where's
my Remy Martin?
- [Tom] Friends are
visiting from Europe.
(metal clicking)
- [Crow] Uh, you're uh,
drinking my commode.
- It is late for you
to visit here.
What is it Eurysteus?
- [Eurysteus] Nothing, but
you have made a mistake.
- [Joel] This is my room.
- No, Hercules will
train Iphitus
to reign here with success.
- [Tom] Right here on ESPN.
- [Eurysteus] Hercules
was Chiron's close friend.
He hasn't forgotten
what's happened to him.
- That took place years ago.
- [Eurysteus]
Hercules is honest,
and honesty always
finds the truth,
even after many years.
- [Crow] Is it Dr. No?
- [Eurysteus] His purpose
for coming here is
to clear Chiron's name.
- [Joel] Is it the Millionaire?
- Perhaps he'll find something
else more interesting.
Emotions, for example.
- Iole.
- [Crow] Oh, it's him, that guy,
whoever it is.
- Young people forget
their purposes sometimes.
- [Tom] These kids today,
I tell ya.
- You'll foresee this
man they say, you'll see.
- I know, I know.
- [Joel] Uh, can I
go to bed now?
- I'll be going now, to
my hiding place.
As you promised, it was
the only reward I got.
- [Pelias] And the gold?
- The gold?
But you need light to
see it well.
It's like blood on my hands.
Bloody.
- [Crow] Pussy.
- Like your brother was.
- [Pelias] Get out.
- Very well, because I
can wait 'til you want me.
- [Tom] Because I can
wait 'til you want me.
- [Joel] And don't slam
the screen door.
Doh.
- [Crow] It's the Punt,
Pass & Kick competition.
- [Tom] It's a Gore
Vidal fantasy.
- [Joel] Would you two
please stop that
and get back to training,
please?
- [Crow] I do solemnly swear.
- No more racing, and
I'm not joking,
your heart's strained, you
can't force it.
- I know Aesculapius, but I
want to finish this marathon.
- Better take him away.
- But I was training for months.
- Go on.
- [Tom] I wish I was a doctor.
- They've all become fanatics
since Hercules arrived.
They seem to worship
nothing but strength.
- Their studies are neglected
for the glory of the arena.
Isn't that so, Orpheus?
- [Joel] Who are you?
- Yes Laertes, for the
moment, poetry languishes.
- [Tom] Hey, can we
play through?
- And my lyre will
soon sing songs
of nothing but
heroes in battles.
- Well look Tifi, here's Argos.
- He seems to be furious.
- [Crow] I'm furious.
- All of you here in the arena?
And have you all
changed to his ways?
Ha, talk to the men, they
speak only of Hercules.
- He's won their hearts.
They won't listen to me.
To my way of thinking,
he could start them battling
against their elders.
- No, Laertes.
- [Joel] Honey.
- Just watch Hercules, a
born master of these things.
If he'll fight here, he can
bring defeat to our enemies.
- [Tom] Hold your cards.
- Look at him, standing
with Castor and Pollux.
- [All] Ew.
- [Orpheus] Deceit does not go
with a man of such qualities.
- [Crow] Hey, what're you
guys lookin' at?
- Look.
- [Joel] There goes one now.
- [Crow] Neat.
- [Tom] Ta da.
- That's very good.
A fine jump.
But next time.
- [Crow] Goofy.
- Try to end up on your feet.
If you want to become
champion, you must work.
- I wanted you to notice me.
I wanna be like you, Hercules.
- And you will be, my boy,
because you have a strong will.
- My father said you put
strength ahead of everything,
but I know you want us to
use our forces
only to serve our intelligence.
(goofy laughter)
- And you are right.
Alright, now, you will
stay by my side
and I'll teach you to fight.
But not only with your hands.
And some day, your friends
and enemies will honor you
and name you the wise.
(horse neighing)
- [Tom] Hey, the pizza's here.
(goofy rhythmics)
- [Joel] Hey everybody, I
just invented the shirt.
- [Crow] Somebody call a cab?
- I might have known who it was.
Pheatus, forgive us, but, don't
you think it's time we go?
He's here.
- Until tomorrow.
- [Joel] He's perfect.
- [Tom] Judd Hirsch.
- [Joel] Uh, we better get
to class, guys.
(crowd grumbling)
- [Crow] Hey, suck it in.
- [Tom] Oh, did ya see that
guy suckin' it in there?
- Get a bow.
The sun is high already.
You sleep too much.
- The pleasures I enjoy must
aggravate you, but it's early,
so please don't start
that eternal nagging,
simply because I delayed
the great Hercules.
- [Crow] Hey, I worked
hard for this body.
- [Joel] Gimme one o' those,
yeah.
- Wait.
Shoot where you are.
- Mmm?
(group heckling)
- My, you've certainly got
a distinguished
assembly of spectators.
- [Tom] Shoot the arrow.
- [Crow] Oh, he's left it way
right of the green, Chris,
over the gallery.
- Why, this distance
is nonsense.
Is it your purpose to
humiliate me so they'll talk?
- In battle?
At this distance, we've
called for the use of the bow.
For shorter distances, the
use of the sword or the spear.
And remember it's not a
question of physical strength.
With a little intelligence,
even a boy like this one.
- [Tom] Hey.
- Can hit a bullseye,
standing where he is.
- Better yet, prove it to me.
Prove to me your head isn't
just a mass of muscle up there.
- [Joel] Well wait a minute now,
my head is a mass of muscle.
- [Tom] Herc, honey, I
brought you a sandwich
and some clean underwear.
- [Joel] Oh-eh-o-lay.
- [Crow] You're lucky
my chick's here.
- [Tom] Come on, Nipples.
- [Joel] Just drink in my back,
huh?
- Come with me.
- [Tom] He's idling her
motor, huh? (leering snicker)
- What's he doing that for?
- Keep still.
- [Joel] Oh, he always does this
when they play miniature golf,
too.
- Now concentrate and
listen to me.
Aim before you wind up.
- [Crow] Keep your left
arm straight.
- Watch the direction and
intensity of the wind.
- [Joel] It ain't over
'til it's over.
- Watch the tops of those trees.
- [Tom] And have some fun.
- That will guide you to
incline your bow
at the proper angle.
- [Crow] The bow?
- [Hercules] Once you've
determined that.
- [Crow] Determining it.
- [Hercules] Let go
of the arrow.
- [Crow] What, this thing that?
- It will have to go
straight out.
- [Crow] Help.
- Here's your bow.
- [Crow] Yes.
- Now watch.
- [Crow] Oh.
- Here.
- [Joel] Aw, knock it off,
Herc, every chance he gets.
- [Tom] Poser.
- [Crow] I can do that.
- [Tom] Oh, you
smell nice today.
- That's it.
- [Crow] And, now let
me get outta the way.
- Just one more inch now.
- I can't do it.
- You must do it.
Steady now.
One more foot.
- [Tom] Give me an inch.
- Shoot.
- [Joel] Wrong, wrong, wrong.
What's new, pussycat? Whoa
- Ah.
- A perfect shot.
- Look at that.
- Ah.
- [Joel] I know him, I date him.
- Well done, my boy.
What's your name?
- Ulysses, son of Laertes.
- Remember what I'm
going to say.
(heckling gibberish)
- One day a bow may
decide your fate.
- [Tom] Now get outta here,
ya bum.
- Listen, no one in all
of this country
has ever beaten me at
discus throwing.
Alright, are you ready?
- [Hercules] I accept.
- [Joel] Think fast.
- Orpheus may win the
discus throw,
his body is built lighter
than Hercules.
(mocking laughter)
And that could work as
an advantage.
- We must wait and see.
- [Tom] Oh, it's Clay Shaw.
- [Joel] Yep,
yep,
and yep.
- [Crow] Would you just
throw the discus?
- [Joel] And yo.
(wind whistling)
- Hey yeah, 137 and
three-quarters.
- I must say it's extraordinary.
- It will take some
doing for Hercules,
if he ever wants to
beat that record.
- Now just wait a minute.
- Come Hercules, we'd
like to see your style.
- [Tom] I bet you would.
- How do you throw the
discus at Thebes?
With both hands?
(derisive laughter)
- [Joel] Oh, that'll cost
him some points.
- [Tom] Yes, let's see,
it's up and over.
- [Crow] Heh-heh, heh-heh, heh.
- [Tom] Yes, one at a
throwing the discus,
it's one, uh yes.
- [Joel] Oh, would you just.
(wind whistling)
- Truly the hands of a god.
- [Crow] Look out, Aeschylus.
- My chariot.
My chariot.
I want my chariot.
- [Tom] Okay, here you
go sir, uh, sir, sir,
you haven't validated yet, sir.
- [Joel] Now don't go
driving all crazy.
It's not worth it.
Oh, he's gone.
- [Tom] The totals on
the board are correct.
Before leaving, we urge you
to check your immediate
seating area.
- [Crow] Get out of my head,
you, no.
(loud whimpering)
- He can beat anybody.
- [Joel] Oh, don't look at
the naughty man, come here.
- [Tom] Oh, I may be the winner,
but I'm goin' home alone.
Maybe not.
- [Crow] Well, I liked it.
Do do do, do do
- [Hercules] Better get
back to Julco.
- No, I want to enjoy
the spectacle.
- [Hercules] Go away.
- I want to see you
battling a lion,
not throwing a discus around.
- [Tom] Why?
- Your tongue is faster
than your sword.
- You take your orders from me.
- Go back, I'm
responsible for your life.
- Your responsible
for my prestige
in front of the people, too.
By the gods, I swear
if you escape the lion,
you won't escape this.
- [Joel] Oh, it all comes
out at once with you.
- [Crow] Bozo the lion.
(lion snarling)
(horse neighing)
- [Tom] Oh.
- [Crow] Kitty.
- [Tom] Come on, you two,
you're irritating the lion.
(horses neighing)
- [Joel] Oh, this is goin'
real well.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- [Crow] Puh, well, I
seem to be okay.
A few scratches.
Ah ho.
(lion growling and snarling)
- [Joel] You know they never
use their scratching posts.
- [Crow] No.
- [Tom] Claude Balls, ladies
and gentlemen, Claude Balls.
- [Crow] I'll get the
water pistol.
- [Tom] Come on, mix it up,
I'm hurt.
Come on, Bert Lahr's a wimp,
come on.
- [Crow] Oh, you know you pet
'em once, they won't go away.
- [Tom] Oh, you got a
dry socket there, pal.
Uh, take me.
(lion snarling)
Aw, Herc, I was kidding.
- [Crow] Oh.
Oh, I'm telling Joan Embery
from the San Diego Zoo.
(snoring)
- [Joel] Ya know, either
this man is dead
or my sundial has stopped.
(fast mumbling)
- Is this your design, oh gods?
Is this why I've come to Julco?
- [Tom] Pretty much.
(horse hooves clopping)
- [Joel] Hi, we came to
get Scruffy, our pet lion.
Oh, my god.
- A chariot arrived in Julco,
like a messenger of death.
- [Crow] So to speak.
- But it didn't tell you
about the victim, I see?
- It may still be you, Hercules.
- [Tom] Alright boys,
back to the precinct.
Let's go.
(siren wailing)
- [Joel] So, lunch?
Oh yeah, you're dead, but still.
- I told you Pelias, I
prophesied doom
if you didn't send him away.
- He's dead, my son.
Oh, cruel gods.
- Useless complaining
to the gods.
Plan your revenge now.
- [Crow] Avoid the rush.
- Revenge my son, (mumbles).
I'll make Hercules
suffer the way I suffer.
- Listen to what I say to you.
- [Tom] Your tunic's
open in the rear.
I can see your bike rack.
- And if you just do that, you
can forget he's invincible.
- [Man] Your highness.
- [Joel] Yeah.
- [Man] Hercules has returned.
- [Crow] Oh, I'll
alert the media.
- [Tom] It's Hercules, why
is everything Hercules, ah?
- [Joel] Hey boss, did
you hear about Hercules?
- [Crow] Yes, I heard
about Hercules?
- [Joel] Now what?
- [Tom] Uh, hi, um, he broke.
Sorry.
(grunting)
- [Crow] Could you give
me a hand here?
- [Joel] Okay, whose
gonna sign for this?
- [Tom] Careful, I'd recommend
a cool storage place.
- [Joel] Uh, could I have
his room, dad?
- [Tom] I love my
dead Greek son.
- [Group] Our work
here is finished.
(sobbing)
- [Tom] Look, no charge, okay?
- No one requested you go
after the lion.
- [Joel] He did it on spec.
- If you hadn't been
so headstrong,
he would still be alive.
- [Tom] But any way, it's
still a nice day, huh?
- The lion is vanquished.
- [Crow] The lion
takes Vanquish?
- The parents of his victims
feel grateful, I suppose.
The danger is past them now.
- [All] Give us Barabbas,
Barabbas, Barabbas.
- But it can't placate me.
- [Joel] Go ahead, let it out,
come on.
- You want only your glory.
You brought the gods'
vengeance on my house.
You'll atone for these things.
- [Tom] You'll atone
for these things.
- You fought the lion.
You'll pay for the things
you believe in.
You'll do what I order you to.
And I swear no man
will help you.
- [Crow] I ain't helpin' him,
you?
- [Joel] Nope.
- I charge you to meet
the Cretan Bull in battle
and may the curse of the
gods be upon you.
- [Tom] Look, can I get
a word in here?
- Until you pay for the
blood of Iphitos.
- [Tom] You are dead,
aren't you?
(crying)
- [Joel] Oh, what a
crummy 4th of July.
(loud marching footsteps)
- [Crow] Sorry ma'am,
got another show.
Just, ah, thanks.
- [Tom] Oh, saw him move,
just kidding, sorry.
- [Joel] Well, I see my chance.
- [Crow] So, uh, why the
long face, kidding of course,
just breakin' the ice.
- Iole, I didn't want to
speak out against your father.
But his punishment's unfair,
and his accusations unjust.
- [Tom] He's just so bogus.
- Yes, I know.
Hercules must listen
only to the gods.
Because he cannot know
the suffering of a woman.
- [Joel] Oh, yeah, it's
a woman thing.
- Listen to me, Iole.
- I don't want to.
Go away.
(sobbing)
- [Crow] Maybe I'll call
Sampson, see what he's up to.
- [Joel] But she likes me,
really.
- [Tom] Wait, wait, you
guys, the party's not over,
I got plenty of cocktails left
with the little
umbrellas in 'em.
Come on.
- [Crow] Well I'm
still immortal,
they can't take that
away from me.
- [Joel] Oh yeah, I'll
clean up the lion.
- [Tom] James A. Michener's
Adventures in Hercules.
- [Joel] Looks like he's doin'
real good,
he's got a paper route.
- [Crow] Oh dang, on top of
everything, my house is on fire.
- [Tom] Shane, come back Shane.
- [Joel] Hey, what's for dinner,
Hop Sing?
- [Crow] There will be patches
of scattered god today,
followed by--
- Why did Iphitos have to die?
Answer me, Sybil.
I cannot understand.
I'm greatly confused.
A man I could crush with
one hand gives me an order,
a woman humiliates me.
- It is not you who is to blame,
Hercules.
Iphitos died simply because
he was not meant to be
King of Julco.
- [Joel] Uh, will you
hand me the extinguisher?
- Now the gods assign a
new labor to you.
They want you to go out
and chance your fate
against the Cretan Bull.
- Enough.
I'm tired of doing all
of these senseless things
for the gods.
When will I be worthy
in the eyes of the gods?
- [Crow] I'm in over
my head here.
- The hour of your
fate is nearing.
Don't rebel against it.
- Now listen to me.
These changes have happened
to me in the last few days.
- [Tom] Male menopause.
- Iole, the way they
punished me.
All of these things help
me to feel in another way.
- [Joel] All tingly.
- I can't stand being superior.
Let me experience the
real things, love or hate.
- Those are mortal states,
Hercules.
- If it's my immortality
making me unhappy,
then I'll do without it.
- That's dangerous, Hercules.
Don't you know how foolish
you'd be to renounce it?
To be born a man and to
see everything die
is not to be immortal.
Stay as you are.
Be a god.
Don't exchange immortality
for fear, pain, and sorrow.
- I want to live like
any other mortal man.
- [Crow] Oh, brother.
- It's my prayer to
have a family.
- [Tom] A nice
two-bedroom apartment.
- I want children of my own.
- [Joel] Herc is a '90s woman.
- To see your
children growing up.
- Pass on, Hercules.
- [Crow] You're barren, pal.
- It's all as you ask.
Now you shall have to
confront your future
and fight using only
your own forces.
Mortal victories or
you'll be defeated.
- Uh, Joel?
You remember the group Hamilton,
Joe, Frank and Reynolds?
- Oh sure, of course I do,
they had uh,
two huge chart-busting hits
when I was a kid in the '70s.
- What were they?
- Oh um, well the first one was
Don't pull your love out
on me, baby, remember?
Don't pull your love
out on me, baby
- Oh sure, I remember that.
Now what was the other hit?
- Oh uh, I don't really
remember the second one,
except that it
sounded a lot like.
- [All] Don't pull your love
out on me, baby, right see.
- How many members did
that band have?
- Oh come on, Crow, that's easy.
They were a quartet, Hamilton,
Joe, Frank and Reynolds.
- Really?
I always thought
they were a duo,
Hamilton Joe Frank and Reynolds.
- No, you guys, it was a trio.
Hamilton Joe, Frank
and Reynolds.
- Wait, they were a quintet.
- How do ya figure that?
- Well, Hamilton, Joe,
Frank, Ann, Reynolds.
- But maybe if Ann Reynolds
is one person, Tom,
that would lead us
all right back
to the whole trio theory.
- Oh.
- Well, with names like that,
why the heck did they even
name the band after themselves?
Hamilton, Joe, Frank and
Reynolds does not exactly
roll off the tongue, like
Dino, Desi and Billy.
- Joel, do you think
we'll ever find the answer
to the Hamilton, Joe,
Frank and Reynolds mystery?
- Well, who can answer my
young friends?
Who can really answer?
- Well, Hamilton, Joe,
Frank and Reynolds.
(beeping)
(screaming)
(clacking)
(thrumming)
(rolling)
(sliding)
(crackling)
(creaking)
(sliding)
(slamming)
- Therefore you may
have come here.
- [Joel] Good morning.
- Only to defraud me.
- I myself heard Chiron
talk about the fleece.
- Your words can't influence
me in what I must do.
You've brought enough
unhappiness to my house.
Do you wanna take my throne now?
- Well, maybe this will
convince Pelias.
- [Tom] Would you just.
(scuffling)
- [Crow] Ooh, look at
the pins on him.
- [Joel] Athletes foot, ew.
- [Tom] Great legs,
whadya think, huh?
(chattering)
- [Crow] I'd kill for
those ankles.
- If I may speak,
I think this discussion
is a waste of time.
- [Joel] No, Larry, you may not.
- If this is Jason and he
tells the truth,
then we must ask the
gods to prove it.
- The Colchis is a long
journey, but if we persist
and take this voyage
as I suggest,
we might find the truth
about King Aeson's death.
- [Tom] Howard Johnson is right.
- I feels the gods favor us
piercing the mysterious Colchis.
- [All] Ew.
- It's perilous and all
our men shall need courage.
- [Tom] Courage.
- For you see, for years
we wanted an opportunity,
and now know the adventure
for which Argo's ship
was destined.
- [Joel] Who is he?
- The poets will write about
this in all the years to come.
- [Crow] Like Rod McKuen?
- How we found the
fleece of gold
or disappeared in the
silence beneath us.
Let the people appraise
the legitimate heir
to the glorious throne of Julco.
- [All] Hail, Dorothy.
- We must be able to
know who he is
the day we come back.
- Orpheus is right, I
shall prepare the boat.
- [Joel] What boat?
- And I shall go, too.
- I also.
- We'll go.
- [Tom] Et tu.
- Do as you must.
The gods have willed you
to decide this.
- [Crow] Rip Torn, ladies
and gentlemen.
- But don't expect me
to wait here.
Tortured by doubt for the
little time that I have.
- [Joel] And I'm not
gonna pick you up, either.
- You have three months
to come back.
Not one day more.
- [Tom] You kids will be
the death of me.
- [Crow] I need a salty dog.
- [Joel] Has anybody
seen my heels?
- [Crow] Eyes front, Carl.
- Be assured of our help.
- What he says is true.
- You can count on me.
- You do look like King Aeson.
- Of course, because
he is Jason.
- Has anyone spoken of Ulysses?
That's me, I'll introduce you.
It's so nice that
you'll let me go.
(laughter)
- [Tom] Live from the
Fontainebleau Hotel.
- Iole.
- [Crow] Oh, that dress,
melts my fillings.
(leering)
- What do you want of me?
- [Joel] Do you have a quarter?
- [Hercules] Don't think I'm
being hostile to your father.
- Isn't that funny?
Then what should I think?
- [Hercules] I'm only
searching for the truth.
- [Tom] You can't
handle the truth.
- Truth?
I feel the truth no longer
matters after what you've done
to him in there.
- Listen to what I have to say.
What I've done is for you.
- I don't belong to you now.
You listen to the
words of Orpheus.
There's a new mission to begin.
One will be covered
with success.
Follow the one you name Jason,
then.
And come back victorious,
like the adventurer you are.
- [Crow] Whoa, back off.
- Do you remember what you
said the first day we met?
- [Tom] Oh, you mean ew.
- That couldn't be happy
as long as the mystery
of your uncle's death
couldn't be cleared up.
Listen, Iole, it's our
destiny to solve it.
- No Hercules.
Your destiny is not mine.
- [Joel] Meh, better take a jump
in that cold fountain, Herc.
- [Crow] Later that same day.
- They'll succeed
I'm sure of it.
They'll return with the
Golden Fleece.
I'll be accused.
They'll kill us all.
- [All] Woo, yay, yes, yes,
very nice.
- Yes, because she's mine.
- It started because of
that man without a sandal.
- That's enough, Pelias.
- These lamentations
aren't going to save you.
- Alright, then.
Help us.
Do you know any way to save us?
I'm ready to do it.
- If Jason's murdered and
since your son is dead,
you must see, you can't expect
your daughter to rule alone.
- No.
You shall never marry Iole.
Monster.
- Their craft's almost
ready to sail.
I could be on it.
Better think it over.
Goodnight.
- [Crow] And now, funny
man Morty Gunty.
- [Joel] Well, you wanna
eat or anything?
- [Tom] Nah, I'm
gonna eat alone.
- [Crow] Nice day for it.
- [Joel] Looks like it's a
big, brawny, hairy, glistening,
two-fisted, manly day.
- [Tom] What a cheap cruise.
- [Crow] I wanna be mortal,
what was I thinking?
(singing in foreign language)
- [Joel] Dennis Day?
- [Crow] Any day.
- Hercules, why don't you sing?
- [Tom] I'd rather not
talk about it.
- Wager it's Iole, hey?
- [Crow] What was that
supposed to mean?
- You're not the man to
act like that.
First they're saying.
- [Joel] Oh, why did I
sit with this guy?
- Then begins that
jealous feeling.
That passes after
you're married,
because then you're too
tired to be jealous.
- [Crow] Shut up.
Steward.
- [Tom] Abe Lincoln
looks cheesed here, huh?
(singing in foreign language)
- [Joel] What, did Herc
get on a swing choir barge?
- Here comes the wind,
get to the sails.
- [Crow] Oh good, this
is the fun part.
I like this a lot
better than rowing.
- [Tom] What are they doing?
(squealing and grunting)
- [Crow] The mighty
canvas, like a giant skin,
hoisted aloft by sinewy hands.
- Time goes slowly here at sea.
I think I'll start a calendar.
One notch for each day.
- [Joel] Well, now that's
a good system.
I would of done something
like three notches,
but he simplified it.
- [Tom] You'd think that
they'd be further away by now.
They're barely past the dock.
- [Joel] Well, no plot
on the horizon.
- [Crow] I wonder what I'm
thinking about?
- [Tom] Where do you want
these place settings, ma'am?
- [Joel] Um, will you
be checking out today?
- You don't speak anymore,
you just keep looking out there.
- [Crow] Keep it up.
- We're all sad, too.
- They never went this
far before, I guess.
- That's enough.
- [Tom] Gee, sorry for
supporting you.
- [Joel] If you're going
to do an intervention,
you're gonna have to be
more persistent than that.
- [All] Man on the floor,
man on the floor, man.
- [Crow] Now what did I
come in here for?
Oh yeah.
No.
- You wait so anxiously.
While my fate is decided.
- Yes, father.
We ask for only peace of mind.
- [Tom] Oh, and the car.
- And if this boy is
really Jason?
- [Crow] Well, he claims
to be, but damn if I know.
- The throne is a burden.
You even wanted to give it up,
you said.
- To begin over again, my child.
No I can't do it.
I know the gods will aid you
and Hercules.
Don't say that.
- [Crow] Oh, daddy.
No, Iole, I would like
to wipe him your mind.
- [Joel] Um, I'm not a hugger.
- [Crow] Well you probably
should have thought about that
before we left.
- [Joel] There go the dumbest
group of guys you'll ever see.
Look at 'em.
- [Tom] Twelve angry Greeks.
- Well get moving, get to work.
- [Crow] Geez, you've got
to take orders
from Pete Townshend in a dress.
- Until later.
- [Joel] Yeah don't
look at our butts.
- [Crow] Okay.
- [Tom] Oh boy (laughter),
you know the bigger they
are, the nicer they are.
- [Crow] Their butts?
- [Tom] No, no.
- [Crow] Oh.
- [Tom] Oh, there you are.
(chattering)
- [Crow] Do you like Hercules?
I think it's kind of a jerk.
- Let's keep together.
Better take this path.
- [Tom] Okay we'll take
this other path.
- [Joel] No I said
stay together.
C&H pure cane sugar
- [Crow] I can quit anytime.
- [Joel] It's a whoopie plant.
- [Crow] Guys, wait for me.
(menacing music)
- [Joel] Attack of the
Mary Martins.
- [Tom] Oh no, we're captured.
- [Crow] Joel what was
that shot about?
- Stay there.
What do you want on this island?
- We presumed the
island was deserted.
Some of us landed to find
water and stock up provisions.
Be assured our
intentions are peaceful.
- Throw down your arms
and follow us.
Queen Antea shall decide.
- [Tom] We
surrender.
(footsteps crunching)
- Ooh.
- [Crow] Oh just think
what they could of hit
if they felt like it.
- [Tom] Oh come on, they
could never do that again,
not in a million years.
Oh, doh.
- [Crow] Even the archers
are beautiful.
- Why not?
Might prove interesting.
(metal clattering)
- [Joel] Not the tunics, guys.
- Follow me.
Where I go, what I am,
who I know
- [Joel] Ho, ho, it's a
wacky sitcom.
- [Tom] Or a wacky satyricon.
- [Crow] Voon, hey,
Skipper, look what I found.
- Say what your name is.
- [Tom] Come here often?
- [Crow] Isn't
everybody here phony?
- Don't you ever talk?
- [Joel] She's an
Ellen Jamesian.
- I think it's
unbelievable that at 60
I'm taking part in an
adventure like this one.
(choking)
- So whether they're
real alright.
I always thought it
was a legend,
the kind of nonsense
invented by poets.
- [Crow] Yeah, we
hear that a lot.
- What do you mean?
Who are they?
- They are the Amazons,
if you want to know.
The population is female.
Absolutely all girls.
- [Crow] Women.
- A society similar to the bees.
- Did you ever hear how
the drones finish?
- Who finish?
- Yes, the male bees
of the tribe.
The females kill them
at the mating season.
- Look at that.
- [Joel] It's us.
- And only men.
- [Crow] It's the Andrea
Dworkin Memorial Cemetery.
- [Tom] So you came to island
for food and provisions.
- Landed here, loved here
and died here.
- [Joel] Sounds okay to me.
- A pity.
- [Tom] That's great,
maybe we should run.
(shrieking)
(laughter)
- Let's not forget.
Who said life sometimes
hangs by a thread?
- [Joel] Bill Baird?
- Shall we be alive tomorrow?
Who's able to say.
So it's best to be happy today.
- [Crow] Who are you,
Bobby McFerrin?
- [Tom] It's the
Bataan Sex March.
- [Joel] It's Little Big Man.
- [Crow] Oh, they're gonna
carve Mount Rushmore.
- [Joel] They've landed on
the island of annoying music.
- [Tom] Gee, I wonder what
it cost to heat this place.
- [Crow] Oh, great, there's
a big line at check-in.
- [Joel] Land of the
Bea Arthurs.
- [Crow] Wow, that's
quite a lobby.
- [Tom] I surrender, rawr.
- [Joel] Guess
what's for dinner?
- [Tom] Manwiches, yeah.
- [Crow] It's the Percy
Faith Orchestra.
- [Joel] Esther Williams.
- [Tom] Aw, I've been
sucking it in for an hour.
I'm really glad you're here.
- Hail to you, milady.
Be assured that these men
and I, from another land,
come in peace to your island.
- [Crow] Yeah right, kill 'em.
- Our aim is simple,
all we want are supplies
and provisions.
And a room somewhere
- I fear you may be ironic.
You see the Amazon people
are dying out.
As you know, we are all women.
We have lost our men.
(thunder claps)
They were all killed years ago,
when they went up the
mountain side.
An earthquake took them.
Now we remain alone here.
- [Joel] Very alone.
- Pity us for the
way we are now.
- [Crow] Gee, I feel bad.
- You'll find we are
valuable allies.
- Excuse my indiscretion.
- [Tom] But that bod.
(high pitched mewling)
- I am called Jason.
- [Joel] No, what are you doing?
- We're from Julco.
This is Argo, Pollux, Laertes,
Castor and Aesculapius.
- [Joel] And Steve.
- We were sailing to
the Colchis,
but a storm forced us to
throw our provisions overboard
and you see, we never tried.
- You shall stay 'til tomorrow
and then go.
- [Tom] And remember
checkout is at noon.
- Now you listen to
what I tell you.
- [Crow] Isn't she great?
She's great.
- Put at the stranger's
disposition all our wine
and all our food.
(cheering)
- You didn't say what
your name is.
- [Crow] They call me Mr. Tibbs.
- My name is Antea,
now you know.
- Would it be
insolent if I asked
about the earthquake story?
- [Tom] I beg your pardon?
- You said the story was
that the earthquake
killed all the Amazon men.
But on the way here,
Laertes told it to me.
- [Joel] So what's the deal?
- Only, according to him, it
happened a hundred years ago.
- And you want to know
about how we survived?
Women living here alone.
- [Crow] Lots of bathrooms.
- Well?
- Fine.
- Let me teach you to swim.
- [Joel] Oh, you're drunk.
- Really, I saw the lake
as we were coming up here.
You'll enjoy it.
- I must admit we were
frightened at first,
your marksmanship was perfect.
- When I finally
lowered the sales.
- [Crow] Hey, it's a mixer.
(crowd chattering)
- [Tom] And, that's when I
got into collecting spoons.
- Seven years after
the eruption.
- [Crow] Excuse me?
- Seafaring men came here,
and they were welcomed
needless to say.
But, we were paid back
with violence and cruelty.
- [Joel] But enough about me.
- It taught us a lesson.
Then the women formed
themselves into an army.
- [Crow] He's pretending
he's interested.
- Now we make sure the
women aren't hurt.
- [Tom] Oh, of course.
- Before they were,
but no man now.
- You kill all the men.
- It proves to us that
we are superior.
- [Tom] Oh yeah, that's
really interesting.
- Men mean nothing
anymore for us.
- [Joel] Oh, whadya know?
- If I should die tomorrow,
I'd be happy to have
sacrificed and dedicated all
to be the queen of this island.
- [Tom] Really?
- But don't your women
ever fall in love?
- Don't you see, love is an
expression never used here.
- [Joel] Except when
it comes to chocolate.
- It has been lost as
time passed.
(laughing)
Please.
- But you're joking,
you must be.
Tell me, do you really hate us?
- [Crow] Yes.
- Women know what you want.
Filled only with your
own desires.
- [Tom] And watching football.
- The gods of created us
Amazons purposely
to punish you for your wrongs.
- [Crow] Oh, punish me, please.
- Not all men are alike.
Some men are full of
kind sentiments.
- [Joel] Like Alan Alda.
- Not just desires.
You know, a woman is
incomplete without a man.
- [Crow] Zing!
- [Joel] Ow, my spine.
(cracking)
- [Tom] The Ooh
Lagoon (laughing).
- [Crow] I see Sparta,
I see Athens,
I see someone.
- [Tom] Um, I'd like to do a
scene from Baywatch, if I may.
- [Joel] By all means.
- [Tom] Now don't you
kids get drunk
and go swimmin' under the dock.
(doodling)
Help, I'm drunk and I've
swam out under the dock.
(gurgling)
Baywatch.
- [Crow] Stay away from
their powerful hind legs.
- [Joel] She's nude.
- [Tom] When congress
goes swimming.
- [Crow] What, did we tap
into the Playboy channel?
- [Tom] And so the man of
the calypso out,
all painted bronze,
Falco cries when in Rome,
and dives into the water.
- One more.
(laughing)
(choking)
- [Joel] Elanore Donahue?
- Oh, you know, you're
really so greedy.
- [Crow] You mean Greeky.
- But, why did we
meet like this?
- [Tom] You wouldn't
leave me alone.
- Brought to me by a
strange adventure,
I was to have another destiny.
- Your destiny
brought you to me.
- [Joel] Destiny rides again.
- You're so ambitious,
be happy in this place.
- But, I feel we must get away,
somewhere, just the two
of us together,
living like men do
everywhere else.
- [Crow] In the suburbs.
- In suffering.
- Don't go, if, as you say,
there is so much suffering.
- [Joel] Yeah, I got mine,
who cares?
- You may go, but here's
where I belong.
- I'll be here with you.
- [Crow] The flowers are
talking to them.
- It's all that I want just
to be with you like this.
(snoring)
To stay by you, to taste
your kisses, hear your voice.
I can't live without you.
(moaning)
- [Crow] Which trip was better?
- [Man] I'd give 10 years of
my life to solve this mystery.
- There's no mystery.
It's perfectly clear.
- [Joel] That guy's got
a saggy diaper
that leaks over there.
- Hercules, Ulysses and Orpheus
are aboard and we see them.
The others know, they've
been gone a week or more.
- [Tom] (grunting)
- [Crow] That's for Gene Wilder.
- [Tom] Eh,
hello.
Hello.
It's me, little boy, hello.
- [Joel] Mm,
yumpcious wax fruit.
- [Crow] Dear Ulysses, don't
eat the fruit, it's poison.
- [Joel] Mm, buttery napalm.
- [Woman] Your feelings
are no concern of ours.
- [Tom] Uh oh, this is turnin'
into a Porky's, isn't it?
- [Woman] The law is the law
and it must be obeyed
by all of us.
You know the law applies
to you as well,
more to you Antea.
Those men shall all be
put to death,
and do it by tomorrow morning.
Jason will be the first.
He must not live to
see the sunrise.
You must act quickly
before the dawn.
- [Antea] I shall do as
the gods command.
- [Tom] Women, kill,
I'm warning.
- [Crow] I'm not going back Jim.
- [Joel] The naked prey.
- [Tom] Come on, wake up
you boozy old sex fiend,
they're gonna kill us all.
- [Crow] What's that?
Waking (mumbling)
- Will you wake up,
please, it's important.
- What's more important
than sleeping?
- [Crow] Except food and sex.
- Crush seeds of poppies
is what I recommend.
The poppy seeds and wine is the
most effective thing I know.
- [Joel] Poppies.
- Like this one?
- Huh, yes.
- Thank you.
- [Tom] He's grown a
victory garden there.
- [Crow] Yay team.
Previously, oh forget it.
- [Joel] Well, this
oughta pick up the movie.
- [Tom] Think it'll rain
is it stays like this?
- Here comes Ulysses.
- [Crow] Look at the poor dope.
- [Joel] Well, I guess I'll
go make breakfast then.
- [Tom] Oh, did I ever tell
you I used to be immortal?
Oh really?
- Well?
- I hope my beverage works.
- [Joel] Should we
wake the guys?
- [Crow] No, this is our time.
Times like these are made
- Well, will you
look over there?
That's something suspicious,
planning something again.
Sneaking away to visit
those Amazons.
- [Joel] Who can blame
'em though, huh?
- Stay on board like slaves.
- Oh, keep quiet, will ya?
- Keep still, all of you.
I want to sleep.
- [Tom] I've got a
voiceover tomorrow.
Whoa.
- [Crow] That's naughty.
- [Tom] Hmm, I'll
say (chuckling)
The Solid Gold dancers.
- [Joel] Mike Brady.
- [Tom] Can I get another
Grolsch over here?
- [Crow] (hiccuping) I
always get this way
at out-of-town
conventions (hiccuping).
- [Joel] Ah, remember,
there's a 30 drink minimum.
- [Crow] They're having
a collective episode.
- [Tom] Sure it's for the
men, but I like it too.
- [Joel] Grapefruits.
- [Tom] Grapefruits,
wonderful grapefruits.
- [Joel] Grapefruits.
- [Tom] Delicious Ruby
Red Indian River--
- Why is this nectar so potent,
my dear.
You look to me like
you're two girls.
Because you're looking at me
with such a sad expression,
but then everyone looks so
melancholy, and they're dancing,
but we're not going to a
funeral this morning (laughing).
- [Crow] Boring.
(laughing)
- [Tom] I love the way he
tells stories.
- [Joel] How's yours?
- [Crow] Not good.
- [Joel] It's a Who
from Whoville.
- [Tom] Send a signal
to rescue us.
- [Joel] Grapefruits,
they're not just
for breakfast anymore.
- [Tom] Delicious juicy
lemon pulp, num, num, num.
Happy, delicious grapefruits.
- [Joel] They are
really good tonight.
- If it would just contain you.
- [Crow] (nervous laughing)
I'll see you in hell.
- I felt so strange
for a minute.
- [Joel] Insert juicy
grapefruit pulp.
- [Crow] Really unclog you,
grapefruit.
(chattering)
Alright, now for the abdominals.
Thank you, thank you.
(laughing)
- Don't go away yet.
I can't sir, house rules,
I'm sorry.
- [Joel] You act like we're
all gonna die or something.
(screeching)
- [Tom] Oh, her face is
drawn to polar north.
- [Joel] Ah, did you have
a Caesar salad for lunch?
- [Crow] I know we've
been dating for an hour,
but I need my space.
- [Joel] That thing is really
pinching her arm there.
(laughing)
(door closing)
(creaking)
(sliding)
clanking)
(shutting)
- [Narrator] And now,
ladies and gentlemen,
The Satellite of Love, in
association with Maboo Mines,
The Wooster Grove
Theater de la Ju Lune
and the Burt Reynolds
Jupiter Dinner Theater
proudly presents the critically
acclaimed tour de force
wherein one robot
single-handedly
portrays Gene Rayburn,
plus all the contestants
on the Match Game.
I'm Tommy Olsen.
Ladies and Gentlemen, we
give you Crow T. Robot
staring in Give 'Em Hell, Blank.
- Hi, I'm Gene Rayburn.
Welcome back to the Match Game.
Well, let's get right to
our next round, shall we?
(throat clearing) Lena
said to Olie,
name the two happiest
days of your life.
Olie said, that's easy
the day I bought my boat
and the day I blank.
The day I bought my boat
Okay, let's see what
we've got up there.
Charles Nelson Reilly.
I was going to say
hinder (laughing).
(bell ringing)
Alright, Brett Somers.
I wrote down
derriere (coughing).
(bell ringing)
Richard Dawson.
Survey says, gluteus maximus.
(bell ringing)
Betty White.
Oh, excuse me.
I wrote down patooti.
(bell ringing)
Fanny Flagg.
Appropriately enough, I
wrote down fanny.
(bell ringing)
And Nipsey Russell.
Well, Olie was a chump, Nena
said this place is a dump,
but I'm gonna say rump.
(bell ringing)
Well, let's see if there
were any other matches,
'cause we're running
out of time,
and I'm afraid, time was
running out for me too.
Those were happy carefree days.
I thought I'd host
Match Game forever,
but alas, not meant to be.
Don't get me wrong, I wish
only the best for Ross Shafer.
The truth is that old
game show hosts like me
are the dying blank.
Charles Nelson Reilly?
Can you hear me?
Brett Somers, are you out there?
Richard Dawson, where are you?
Fanny Flagg, answer me.
Betty White, speak to me.
Nipsey Russell, don't
leave me like this,
alone and afraid.
There is no creature loves me,
and if I die, no
soul shall pity,
wherefore should they, since I,
myself,
find in myself no
pity to myself.
Please God, don't do this to me,
don't kick me in
the patootie.
Ah, who the heck am I to
feel sorry for myself,
my show brought laughter
and joy to millions.
I've had a good life.
Goodnight folks.
- Let's go.
- [Joel] Okay.
(chattering)
- [Tom] Spread out,
I'll handle this.
- Hercules.
- [Joel] Yo.
- Turn the boat around, we
want to go back to the island.
- Orpheus, Ulysses,
take the tiller.
I've decided to go ahead.
- What?
- [Joel] I said, I've
decided to go ahead.
(sirens calling)
- [Tom] You can hear their
civil defense sirens.
- Well, what are you
waiting for?
- Me?
I have a very sick
friend I must visit.
- [Crow] Oh, get a day job.
(laughing)
- [Tom] I don't get it.
So long, farewell,
Auf Wiedersehen
(sirens singing)
- Come on, man the oars.
- [Crow] Or, oar the mans.
- [Tom] It's a Gap
Jeans commercial.
- Orpheus, let's have a song.
- [Joel] A song.
Liar, Liar
- Now sing along with us.
(signing in a foreign language)
I need wind in the sail.
- [Tom] Herc's getting
lusty and oily again,
let's hit is fellas.
- [Crow] Oh yeah, this
is way better
than being on the island.
- [Tom] Maybe if we go higher up
we won't hear Gordon
McRae down there.
- [Joel] I don't like
this anymore than you do.
- [Crow] Sad, really.
- [Tom] Your Ohio
State Buckeyes.
- [Joel] Oh, knock it
off Jerkules.
- [Tom] We forgot the
words to this part.
- [Joel] See, they're
still there.
- [Crow] Maria Callas.
- [Tom] Musical song.
Sail away
- [Tom] He's carving a piano.
- [Joel] Oh.
- [Crow] Hey, ah, oars are
supposed to be broad and flat,
no wonder they're not
getting anywhere.
- If this be the Colchis.
- [Tom] Let me live
is as a blonde.
- [Man] Why do they go
ashore so early?
Couldn't they wait for daylight?
- [Joel] Maybe there's
Amazons on the island.
- [Man] The others follow.
- [Crow] This is a
busy off-ramp.
- [Tom] This island bites,
it's like totally Amazons.
- [Crow] We surrender.
Anybody?
- [Joel] We're ready
to be captured.
- [Tom] It's Swiss
Family Popodopolis.
- [Crow] How about a song, Herc?
- [Joel] There's probably
a strip mall there now.
- [Tom] Hey, Commando Cody.
- [Joel] Hey, this is real fun,
Herc.
- [Crow] It's great, no really,
it is.
- [Tom] Ooh, hey hairy dudes.
Hey, it's the Jim
MacNakowski, Tommy Chong,
Gilbert Gottfried, Gino
Vannelli Tribe.
(screaming)
- [Joel] Well,
they're not Amazons,
but when in Rome fellas.
- [Crow] Thank you
Hercules, this is wonderful.
- [Joel] Man, they're really
not very good savages,
are they?
The top of that tail looked
like the Nutty Professor.
- [Crow] Don't touch the hair.
- [Tom] Ah, here,
give him to me.
I'll do it myself.
Oh, hello.
- It's something out
of a bad dream.
- [Crow] Jim Cutta.
Jim Cutta.
(groaning and chuckling)
Huh, must be time for
savage supper.
- [Tom] See, this can
still be fun.
- [Crow] Okay, how about a song?
- Jason, where is Jason?
- [Joel] Oh, he's reading
comics up in the bushes again.
- Jason.
(eerie vibration)
- [Crow] Wow, good thing I left
the Golden Fleece out to dry.
- [Tom] A lone ram
committed suicide today.
- [Crow] Ah, can I help you sir?
- [Joel] Oh wait, I thought
they said golden grahams
not golden ram.
Hey, I feel the earth
move under my feet
(chuckling)
- [Joel] Gilligan.
- [Crow] Mulch strikes back.
- [Tom] Oh, nice doggy,
good pooch.
- [Crow] I thought those
things were extinct.
- [Tom] It's the future site
of Jurassic Industrial Park.
- [Crow] Huh.
- [Joel] Throw him a Milk Bone.
- [Tom] Big one.
- [Crow] Finally a cool part.
(Humming Benny Hill Theme Song)
- [Tom] Welcome to the
land before time.
- [Joel] Man, I'd hate to
see his litter box, you know.
- [Crow] Look, I don't need
the Golden Fleece, you keep it.
- [Tom] Why must I lash
out at everyone I meet?
- [Joel] Hey, I just want
to borrow the Golden Fleece.
Could I just try it on?
- [Crow] You can see
why this film isn't good
for the tourist trade.
- [Tom] Negotiations
for the fleece continued
into the night.
(monster roaring)
- [Joel] Oh, come on,
he just wanted to play.
- [Tom] Oh, oh boy,
that really, oh, golly,
oh boy, whoa.
- [Crow] Creature.
- [Tom] The money is in
the (sighing).
- [Joel] You know that monster
never read Getting to Yes.
Mmm.
- Mmm.
- [Crow] How's he gonna
strap that dinosaur
to the top of his car?
- [Tom] Hmm, it's a bath mat,
what do they want
with a bath mat?
- [Joel] Oh, really up close
it's not really that golden,
it's kind of more of
a burnt umber.
- [Crow] Raw sienna.
Wash separately in cold water?
Hang to dry?
Doh.
- [King] My brother killed me.
- [Crow] Wow, it talks.
- [King] Palius is the man
who struck me as I slept.
May the gods forgive him
for what he did.
- [Tom] How could he have
written it after he died?
- [King] Persecute and curse
him if he harms my son.
- [Crow] Oh, I've read this one.
- [King] I commit Jason
into your hands, oh gods,
and I ask of you
to free his thoughts
from revenge,
for no more blood must be shed.
- [Joel] Yeah, wouldn't that
dinosaur love to hear that now.
(chuckling)
- [Crow] Thank you gods,
thank you so bloody much.
- [Joel] What?
- Yours was the deed of a king.
We acknowledge you as
sovereign of Julco.
- [Tom] Were you watching
all this time?
You guys.
- On whom will our
vengeance fall?
- On no one.
- [Crow] On no one.
- It was the last
request of the king.
- [Joel] Play Stardust.
- It is his will.
He pities those who
take revenge.
You'll return this to Julco.
- [Tom] For a store credit.
- You'll place the Golden
Fleece behind the throne.
- Oh king, it's wise to forgive,
but you'd be wiser to look deep
into the eyes of the man
you've forgiven.
- I follow only what my
father commands
and what my conscience dictates.
- [Crow] You got a plastic
bag for this thing?
Maybe a wooden hanger?
- I must do it.
I'll take the responsibility.
- [Joel] I'll walk it and
feed it and call it Gold.
- [Crow] Sit, stay, good fleece,
good.
- [Joel] Nah, he'll
probably send it UPS.
- [Tom] And now, before
your very eyes,
the Golden Fleece will
escape from this trunk
in just minutes.
- [Crow] Wow, look, it's
been one, two,
well, it's been a long time.
- [Joel] 2,000 flushes.
- [Tom] Hey, mom, dad, hi.
I loved camp.
You should have seen,
this one island there
were girls and stuff.
- [Crow] Respective
honeys we're home.
- We made it in three months.
Where's Hercules, do you know?
- [Tom] Uh, we thought
he was with you.
- There he is.
- Look Ulysses.
- [Tom] Oh, Hercules,
the first postal worker.
- Where is the Golden Fleece?
- Stolen from under out noses.
- [Crow] Duh, duh, duh.
- [Tom] I'm back and
I'm mad as hell.
- Listen, now beware of Jason.
Jason is king.
Jason will judge you.
- Don't forget that we'll fight.
- You will never beat Jason.
- Don't be too sure, because
the Golden Fleece is ours now.
- That's enough, everybody
will know you're thieves.
- [Tom] Doh.
- [Joel] Going down Mr.
Hercules?
- [Crow] Hey, no one said
they had one of those.
- [Tom] Ah, typical, while
the rest of us are unloading,
Hercules is nowhere to be found,
man.
- [Joel] This is my room.
- What is this for?
- You're not to leave your
room, the king's orders.
- Orders, you say?
- [Crow] And just how
long am I grounded?
- Tell me, where is Hercules?
- We know nothing about it.
- [Tom] Right guy.
- But that's ridiculous,
holding us in this way.
- Don't be worried Iole.
Now that Jason's here,
they'll decide who the
king of Julco is.
- Iole, Hercules.
- [Joel] Malcolm X
is over there.
- In there, locked up.
- Watch the sentry.
- [Crow] Always do (giggling).
- [Tom] Oh, this set is for
their big closing number.
- [Joel] Daddy, there's
a bunch of boys outside.
- [Crow] No, wait, go back,
shut up, shh, shh, quiet.
- That will keep him
quiet for a while.
- [Crow] So, anyway,
do you like my helmet?
- [Joel] You know, it's
hard for them
to get any flatter
against that wall.
- [Crow] That guy's
always been asking me out.
I don't want to see him.
- [Tom] Here, wait, let me help.
- [Crow] It's better if I do it.
(chattering)
- [Joel] That is a
lumpy mattress.
- Hercules.
- [Crow] Can I have
the checkbook?
(wind blowing)
- [Joel] Oh, good one.
- The door does not open
from the inside.
We are trapped in
here like he is.
- [Crow] That's why it's
called a prison.
- No, he's still alive.
- You report that your
journey's been successful.
- [Tom] Eh, pretty much.
- That you found the Colchis,
and in the Colchis you
found the Golden Fleece.
May I look at it?
- [Joel] No.
- Where is Hercules?
- [Crow] Where isn't Hercules?
- If I give up my throne,
I must have your proof,
not Hercules.
- Tell me, I demand it.
- You already assume the
tone of a king.
- [Tom] Dah, Herc head hurt.
Where Herc?
Who Herc?
Dah.
- But now you dare to
issue commands.
Bring to me the fleece and
I will give you the throne.
But I promise that if I
find you have lied to me,
you will be condemned
and put to death.
- [Joel] And I mean
it this time.
- I told you, the fleece
has been stolen.
You can ask your own men here.
- [Tom] Tada.
- They're your partners,
if it comes to that.
I want the fleece now.
If the fleece is yours,
show it to me.
- [Crow] Actually
it's Thinsulate.
- I know you can't,
because you're an imposter
and your men are traitors.
Arrest them all.
- [All] You have the
right to remain silent.
- [Joel] Hey, somebody
find the fleece.
- [Tom] Well, Gary had it last.
- [Crow] I gave it to Rick.
- [Tom] Oh, you.
- [Crow] No wonder he
had a hard time sleeping.
- [Tom] What the hell.
I couldn't.
- [Joel] Oh my.
I knew it, now he'll be
dragging those around the house.
- [Tom] Thanks buddy.
- [Crow] You got it pal.
- [Tom] Ooh.
- [Crow] Right in the
groinitalogical area.
- [Tom] The groinular region.
- [Joel] Man, it must
be south central Greece.
- [Tom] Later, I'm a
little busy right now.
I'm Herc and I'm irked.
- [Crow] I can explain
everything (stuttering).
- [Joel] Why didn't
anybody wake me?
- [Tom] Ha, missed me,
now you've got to kiss me.
- [Joel] Oh, he's gonna
have to wear a turtleneck
for the next week.
- [Crow] What are you doing?
Keep a way from me.
Oh (groaning).
- [Tom] Climbin' halfway
through hell in Greece
just to find some
stupid sheepskin.
Doh, gah, I hate these things,
oh.
- Hercules.
- [Joel] Well, he's just
invented the weed whipper.
- [Tom] Weed whipper, ooh.
Yee-who.
- [Crow] Oh, you're here.
- [Joel] Hey, thanks
for thowin' in gramps.
- Very good, that's the way.
- [Tom] That came
out of nowhere.
- [Crow] This is a weird
chain of events.
- [Tom] Doh.
- [Joel] Chains don't kill
people, Hercules kills people.
- [Tom] It's not
worth it fellas,
let's meet in the break room.
- [Crow] Boy, Herc can
really clear a room.
- [Joel] Taste it all,
Diet Hemlock.
- [Tom] I have a delicious
poison in the morning,
and that's it.
- [Joel] That's acrylic.
- [Crow] Now it's a
well-done Golden Fleece.
- [Tom] Ah, dad, let me
guess, something's wrong.
- Iole.
- [Crow] Lady-oh-o-ho.
- Men sometimes make mistakes,
and now mine have
caught up with me.
- [Joel] That's what Michael
Milken probably said.
- So badly.
Jason should reign in Jalco.
- [Tom] Men are such babies
when they have a head cold.
- Tell me about everything now.
You mustn't lie any longer.
- My dear, it's useless.
The poison's working well.
- Poison, father.
- [Crow] That was mine.
- You mustn't regret
anything daughter.
- [Tom] But, dad,
before you die,
will you sign my report card?
- Go away with Hercules.
He's a good man.
- [Joel] You know, if you
would have said
that a half-hour ago, none
of this would have happened.
- Now, gods take me to
the Land of Shadows.
May I be forgiven.
Schools out for summer
- [Crow] Well, that chain thing
is still workin' real well.
- [Tom] This morning a
lone chainman terrorized
downtown Athens, no
motive was apparent.
- [Joel] Oh, not this again.
Any time something
doesn't go his way.
- [Crow] This is how he
always closes his act.
- [Tom] Is that a
supporting beam?
Good, that'll do.
(groaning)
The National Guard was called
in to help quell the violence.
(groaning)
- [Crow] Hey, Herc, we were
coming to congratulate you.
- [Joel] Ah, Mr. Hercules,
they just surrendered
and gave us the palace.
- [Crow] Oops.
- [Tom] We probably should
have gotten out first, huh?
- [Crow] Oh man, if this
were in sense around,
this would be so great.
- [Joel] Well, we could vibrate.
Alright, we're leaving.
All you had to do was
say something.
Gol.
- [Narrator] Now
there is justice,
and the clouds over
Julco pass away.
Out of great sorrow and
spilled blood,
the forces of good are
sometimes born.
Hercules and Iole are leaving
now to find a new happiness.
- [Tom] Six fun-filled
weeks in Jamaica.
- [Narrator] Where
justice and peace will be
with them again.
Farewell Hercules.
- [Joel] Bye now.
- [Narrator] Farewell Iole.
Life awaits you with all its
glory and all its shadows.
- [Tom] Go forth graduates.
- [Narrator] But, even through
the most difficult tasks
the gods may prepare for you.
- [Crow] Herc and Iole
really had a rocky dating
and engagement period.
- [Tom] So, like, ah,
you want to grab a bite,
or maybe lay out on the
ledo deck or somethin'?
- [Joel] Or is it?
- [Tom] I doubt it.
(siren voicing)
- [Crow] Valley High.
What ever happened
to these guys?
- [Joel] I don't know,
it's kind of inconclusive.
- [Tom] Oh, I know, you
see, Hercules got a job
as a prep cook for a while.
He got fired for tokin'
up on the job.
He said it was just
because the manager
didn't like the Greeks.
And Iole did data entry
at Fingerhut.
- [Crow] Did they have any kids?
- [Tom] No, Herc couldn't
perform his husbandly duties,
if you know what I mean.
Well, they adopted Ulysses,
but he became a real
troublesome kid.
You know, he busted into
a cabin up north
and took some fishing gear.
He was on probation for a while.
I heard he's got connection
to a string of chop shops.
- [Crow] But Hercules and Iole
really loved each other, right?
- [Tom] Well, it depends
on how you define love.
You know, for Iole, it
got really hard
to come home from Fingerhut,
night after night,
see this big demigod
sitting on the couch,
slamming back Limeys
and watching TV.
Well, then Herc went
through rehab
and he started selling
Kirbys door to door.
Then one day he ran into an
Amazon he knew from the island,
this Debby.
Pretty soon Debby was
calling him at home all hours
and driving past his house
and stuff, all the time.
Iole just flipped out and then
she left and took Ulysses.
- [Crow] And Jason,
what about Jason?
- [Tom] Jason, he sold
the Golden Fleece
and bought himself a
Rupp Mini Bike.
His family moved a lot, so
he was in and out of schools,
never one place for more
than a couple of months.
Well, he quit school at 15
and started doing standup
comedy on the road.
And then one night he
freaked out on stage
after some guy heckled
him about Madea,
not to mention that he refused
to drive a headliner to
Fargo one time.
So, he didn't get much
work after that.
Then he was killed in a
tragic boating accident,
involving the Argo.
You know, there was some
taunts from cruel crew mates,
and there was a case of St.
Pauli Girl.
- [Joel] Are you done?
- [Tom] No I'm not.
- [Joel] Yes you are.
- [Tom] But what about
crayon, you remember crayon?
He was the one who
went out to the.
(slamming)
(shutting)
(slidding)
(closing)
(slamming)
(shutting)
- So, Tommy boy, by my
calculations,
that comes out to be about
15 Amazon women a piece.
- Yeah, okay, so
it's 15 a piece.
I admit those are good odds,
but what good would it be?
Who wants a bunch of
dumb old girls around.
(sighing)
I mean, there'd be curling
irons all over the bathrooms
and hair clogs in the showers,
not to mention them
wearing our shirts.
- Tom, are you even
paying attention?
Seems pretty obvious to me
that if Amazon women were
to take over the ship,
you and I would not have
to lift a finger.
They'll cook, they'll clean,
they'll empty the load pans.
- Load pans.
- Squeegee the windows
and peel grapes for us.
- Wow.
- And feed them to us.
They even like to go
horseback riding and swimming.
- Wow, well, when you
put it that way,
I guess I could put up
with a few nylons hangin'
in the bathroom, you know.
Boy, all our chores
done, snacks on demand,
lunch every day, kiss bye,
man, we'd have it made.
- I know, I know--
- Okay, okay, listen you guys.
I've heard every word
you said and I want you
to know it makes me just sick.
- What, what?
Were were just saying
that Amazon women love
to do stuff for men.
- Listen, in the first place,
you're not men, you're robots,
and in the second place,
not all women carry
curling irons around,
and in the third place,
you've got Amazons all wrong.
It's like, they were
noble warriors
that didn't need men at all.
It just so happens that
the filmmakers decided
to take a few liberties
with ancient Greek history
and add some sexual titillation,
and you rummies bought it.
(horn honking)
Oh, we got a ship
coming into range.
Give me rocket number nine.
(horn honking)
Hey, who are you?
- Oh, hi, I'm Elaine and
this is Carol.
You know, I must have
taken a wrong turn
at the Piggly Wiggly.
You know, we're looking
for the paper drive.
- [Crow] Well, I can see
by your T-shirt
that you're an Amazon?
- Card-carrying since '67.
- Jeffrey gave us
these T-shirts.
He's my Cindy's youngest.
Cute, I am tellin' ya,
that kid, he's got--
- That's great.
Could you tell us if
you're gonna conquer us
or take us over or somethin'?
- Oh, heavens no, whose
got the time?
It used to be a full-time thing,
now we just conquer
men for charity.
It's real, real fun.
- Ah, well, in that case,
maybe you could help my
friends and I get out of space
and take us back to
Earth or somethin'?
- Oh no mister, you boys knew
you were gonna be in space,
you should of arranged a ride.
I am not mom's taxi.
- Yah, you kids can walk.
It's nice out.
- Well, listen, we gotta run.
It's nice meetin' you fellas,
buh-bye.
Nice kids.
- So, those were Amazons, eh?
Nice, but not at all
what I expected.
- No, not at all.
- Yeah, me neither.
Geez, they seemed like
somebody's moms or something.
She said they were semi-retired,
but still I imagine an
Amazon being a noble warrior
with one cut off and--
(throat clearing)
Listen, let's just, ah,
I'm not feeling very good.
Let's hurry up with the mads,
and I'm gonna lay down, you can
make me a soup and sandwich.
- Okay.
- Come in sirs, please.
- Oh, Frank, bring me that memo.
Oh, Frank, bring me some coffee.
Yes, I'm Dr. Forester, I'm
king of the whole world.
(groaning)
(laughing) Sorry, I
didn't mean to.
I was just about to.
- Push the button perhaps?
- You know me so well.
(electronic music)
- He's something out
of a bad dream.